[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first motion picture that was longer than one hour was made in this country.", "correct_answer": "Australia", "incorrect_answers": ["England", "France", "The USA"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who performed the song The Hammer Goin Down on the Black Dog soundtrack?", "correct_answer": "Chris Knight", "incorrect_answers": ["David Lee Murphy", "Gary Allan", "Steve Earl"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which state is famous for being the site of a series of major earthquakes in 1811 and 1812?", "correct_answer": "New Madrid, Missouri", "incorrect_answers": ["Hilo, Hawaii", "San Francisco, California", "Trenton, New Jersey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do we call the square root of negative one?", "correct_answer": "i", "incorrect_answers": ["log(x)", "e", "Pi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the Barenaked Ladies song that is played in the movie American Pie?", "correct_answer": "One Week", "incorrect_answers": ["Brian Wilson", "If I Had a Million Dollars", "Pinch Me"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Internet Explorer, Opera and Mozilla are examples of what?", "correct_answer": "Web browsers", "incorrect_answers": ["Internet service providers", "Hypertext transfer protocols", "Search engines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the diet of the Great Blue Heron, found in North and Central America, consist of?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Birds", "Reptiles", "Small mammals"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is high in Vitamin E?", "correct_answer": "Sunflower seeds", "incorrect_answers": ["Liver", "Eggs", "Peas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From which of the Terminator movies is the popular catchphrase Hasta la vista, baby?", "correct_answer": "Terminator 2: Judgment Day", "incorrect_answers": ["Terminator 3: Rise of the Machines", "The Terminator", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the mountain peak near the volcano Snaeffelsyokull where the journey in Journey to the Center of the Earth begins.", "correct_answer": "Skartaris Peak", "incorrect_answers": ["Larsen Peak", "Kanut Peak", "Thor Peak"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which term means fear of gravity?", "correct_answer": "Barophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Basophobia", "Bolshephobia", "Bacillophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the Spanish word vainilla, from which the name of the spice vanilla originated?", "correct_answer": "Little pod", "incorrect_answers": ["Sweet aroma", "Small wonder", "Milky flavor"]}]